

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Lead of UI/UX design team at Coders Crew organisation, March 2018 – now (non-profit)

I designed websites (UX and UI side). I created an onboarding plan for newcomers and lead a few design projects. Teamwork, cooperation, hard work and passion are the main drivers in my team. Leading a group of passionate UX designers, who want to develop their skills and gain new experience.

Tools: pen and paper, Figma, Adobe xD, Adobe Illustrator, Slack, Jira

# UX designer / Customer Documentation Engineer at Nokia, July 2017 - now

As a UX designer, I redesigned a Nokia's documentation portal (used internationally over 30 000 users). I worked in a team, with two graphical designers. (UX research, interaction design, sketching, wireframes, to visual design, and development phase). Then, I designed two additional web applications for technical writers, to empower search engine functionality by taking advantage of machine learning and DITA tags. On a daily basis, I work remotely with three developers teams overseas (Agile Methodology).

Tools: pen and paper, Nokia's solutions, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe xD, Jira

## Designer at Mamabu online store, Sept. 2016 - Jan. 2017

As a product designer, I redesigned and developed the UI of blog.mamabu.pl (WordPress). Identified and evaluated online store navigation by categorizing content - funnelling traffic through content. Then, as a UX writer, I edited the website's content. In a meanwhile, I was responsible for contacting manufacturers, business partners and influencers to increase conversion ratio.

Tools: pen and paper, Adobe Illustrtor, WordPress

### Product Designer and Marketing at Euroimpex S.A, Feb. 2015 - June 2017

I cooperated with programmers, and sales team to improve product's UX. I expanded the cloud-based product UI by new features. I was responsible for marketing campaigns, evolving design and experience of the cloud-based solution for schools and the cloud-based printing solution for business. I learned the most when I took care of redesigning Extranet information structure (preparing the new structure of the company's information architecture, infographics and guidelines for employees).

Tools: pen and paper, MS Office, Photoshop

## Member at non-profit Business Centre Club, Oct. 2014 - June 2017

Together with a team, I organised the BOSS Festival, which is the biggest business festival in Poland. I conducted classes at Wrocław High Schools which aimed at showing to students how entrepreneurship is important in our times.

# **EDUCATION**

Wrocław University of Economics, 2014-2019

Master's degree: Business Informatics, graduated summa cum laude (5.0)

Thesis: "Accessibility in the modern user interface design. Evaluation and redesign of the user interface."

Bachelor's degree: Business Informatics, graduated summa cum laude (5.0)

Thesis: "Innovation in Modern User Interface Design. Conceptual Evolution,
Technological Drivers, and Quality Factors."

UX Course at Volvo UX Academy, 2019

European Information Technologies Certification Institute in Brussels, 2018
Computer Graphics Academy - online

#### **ABOUT ME**

#### Experience Designer ~ Accessibility guard

I've been designing digital experiences for 3 years. I believe great product design comes from a focus on the right questions, not the right answers.

Throughout my experience as a designer, I've had the pleasure of working with some talented and passionate people, striving for a shared goal in created the best experience for the end user and also, the clients.

Working as a designer often takes me out of my comfort zone and forces me to learn new things. That is why, I simply love this profession.

# **SKILLS**

Research

Heuristics evaluation

**UX** Design

Sketches, Wireframes, Prototypes

Visual (UI) Design

**Product Design** 

Accessibility-based design

User-cantered design

Native and RWD design

Sketch, Figma, UXpin

Adobe Illustrator and Adobe xD

Canva

Slack and Jira

HTML

Cooperation with developers and PM

# **CONTACT**

www.izabellacreates.com (online portfolio)
www.linkedin.com/in/izabellatokarska
instagram.com/izabellacreates/
izabella.ux@gmail.com
(+48) 512-268-225